[{"id":1,"question":"What type of relationship is defined as one resource existing only if another parent resource exist-for example, pages in a book?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Partial`","`dependent`","`associative`","`linked`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":2,"question":"Which URL pattern is recommended when working with one resource and a collection of resources?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`/companies/{id} and/company`","`/company/{id} and/companies`","`/companies/{id} and/companies`","`/company/{id} and/company`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":3,"question":"When dealing with JSON web Tokens (JWTs), what is a claim?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`data in the token`","`Ownership`","`a permission`","`and integer`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":4,"question":"Which REST constraint specifies that knowledge and understanding obtained from one component of the API should be generally applicable elsewhere in the API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Uniform Interface`","`Client-Server`","`Stateless`","`Chacheable`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":5,"question":"What would you enable to allow a browser on another site to make an AJAX request to your API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`HTTP`","`REST`","`OPTIONS`","`CORS`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":6,"question":"APIs commonly use webhooks to **_**.","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`notify other systems of an event`","`catch error faster`","`improve error logging`","`log additional data`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":7,"question":"What is the underlying goal of all APIs?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`to add new technologies to an organization's infrastructure.`","`to share features and functionality with other system.`","`to move infrastructure to the cloud.`","`to appease the latest digital transformation effort.`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":8,"question":"Which is a common command-line tool for using or exploring an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`bash`","`curl`","`ssh`","`powerShell`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":9,"question":"What is the modern specification for describing an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`OpenAPI (Swagger)`","`WADL`","`WSDL`","`OAuth`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":10,"question":"Which HTTP verb is normally used to update or create a resource in an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`SUBMIT`","`WRITE`","`POST`","`CREATE`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":11,"question":"What is one benefit of server-side caching in APIs?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Mobile app work better.`","`It improves uptime.`","`It offers better security.`","`It reduce load on servers.`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":12,"question":"Your API resource does no allow deletion, and a client application attempted to delete the resource. What HTTP response code should you return?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`409 Conflict`","`400 Bad Request`","`406 Not Acceptable`","`405 Method Not Allowed`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":13,"question":"What is OpenID Connect?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0`","`the new name for SAML 3.0`","`a modern replacement for API keys`","`an SSO competitor for OAuth 2.0`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":14,"question":"What is one benefit of GraphQl over REST approaches?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`flexible querying/responses`","`more stable APIs`","`compatible with more gateways`","`more secure by default`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":15,"question":"Which REST constraint specifies that there should be no shared context?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Stateless`","`Client-Server`","`Uniform Interface`","`Cacheable`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":16,"question":"What purpose does a User-Agent serve?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`It identifies the user ID.`","`It identifies the client application or SDK.`","`It identifies if the API should expect a user authentication.`","`It identifies if the API should accept microservice traffic.`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":17,"question":"If you were to add versioning by using the Accept and Content-Type header, what would be the correct format of the header value?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`application/json`","`application/json_version2`","`text/html`","`application/vnd.myapp.v2+json`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":18,"question":"What is one benefit that OAuth provides over an API key approach?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`A token is encrypted.`","`A token is encoded.`","`A token is scoped to the use case.`","`A token can be shared between systems.`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":19,"question":"The ability to execute the same API request over and over again without changing the resource's state is an example of _.","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`stateless architecture`","`idempotency`","`a uniform interface`","`cacheability`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":20,"question":"What component can you use to wrap legacy architectures or protocols into a REST interface for easier consumption and integration?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`API proxy`","`API gateway`","`OpenAPI`","`OAuth authorization server`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":21,"question":"What protection does a JSON Web Token (JWT) offer to mitigate tampering with its contents?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`transport over SSL`","`encrypted payload`","`a signature`","`encoded payload`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":22,"question":"What OAuth term is used to represent permissions?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`token`","`scope`","`claim`","`back channel`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":23,"question":"What additional type of token would you see when using OpenID Connect?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`ID token`","`refresh token`","`access token`","`auth code token`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":24,"question":"What should you add to a Cache-Control response header to specify that a response should not be stored in an intermediary cache?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`no-proxy`","`client-only`","`restricted`","`private`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":25,"question":"Which OAuth grant type can support a refresh token?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Authorization Code Grant`","`Client Credentials Grant`","`Implicit Grant`","`Authentication Grant`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":26,"question":"Using OAuth, what scope would you request for write access to the API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`It varies from API to API.`","`admin`","`write`","`read-write`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":27,"question":"Which property would you use to include subresources directly into a JSON document?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`_embedded`","`resources`","`subresources`","`_links`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":28,"question":"What is the best way to track SDK and version usage?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`tracking downloads`","`Accept headers`","`user agents`","`polling users`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":29,"question":"Which REST constraint allows for the presence of caching, routing, and other systems between the client and server?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Layered System`","`Stateless`","`Client-Server`","`Cacheable`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":30,"question":"Which content is best to include in your documentation?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`your tech stack`","`reasoning for your naming schema`","`your mission statement`","`sample code`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":31,"question":"What metric tracks overall availability for your API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Response Time`","`Time to First Hello World`","`TTL`","`Uptime`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":32,"question":"What is the recommended method and URL pattern for retrieving a specific user?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`GET /user/{id}`","`GET /users/{id}`","`GET /user?id={id}`","`GET /users?id={id}`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":33,"question":"What is the purpose of a link relation?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`to describe relationships between resources or actions`","`to describe subresources related to the current one`","`to link two resources together`","`to describe a resource and its purpose`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":34,"question":"When building SDKs, which languages should you support?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["Java, Javascript, and .NET","and you can support","PHP, Python, and Go","the languages that your target users use"],"answer":[3]},{"id":35,"question":"Which property would you use to include references to other resources in a JSON document?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`resources`","`_embedded`","`subresources`","`_links`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":36,"question":"What is OAuth?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["an authorization framework for granted delegated access","an approach to single sign-on for APIs","a method for API authentication","HTTP Basic Authentication 2.0"],"answer":[0]},{"id":37,"question":"What should your API documentation describe?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["JSON","HTTP","common use cases","your tech stack"],"answer":[2]},{"id":38,"question":"What is the purpose of an OAuth refresh token?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["to share user profile information","to update an API configuration","to keep a web session active","to retrieve an access token"],"answer":[3]},{"id":39,"question":"What is Time to First Hello World?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API","how long it takes to start a new programming language","how long it takes to install your SDK","how long it takes to read your documentation"],"answer":[0]},{"id":40,"question":"Which response header tells the client and intermediaries that the response is not to be cached anywhere?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["Cache-State: none","Expires:-1","Cache-Control: no-cache","Cache-Control: no-store"],"answer":[3]},{"id":41,"question":"What component hides the distinctions or boundaries between various microservices from end-client applications?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`API gateway`","`API logging `","`a layered system `","`API proxy`"],"answer":[0]},{"id":42,"question":"The textbook approach to api versioning is to use **_**.","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`common knowledge`","`URLs`","`no versioning`","`the Accept header`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":43,"question":"Which is the most secure method to transmit an API key?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`URL parameter`","`Authorization header`","`Base64 encoding`","`Basic Auth`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":44,"question":"Within Oauth, what component validates the user's identity?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`client`","`not specified`","`authorization server`","`resource server`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":45,"question":"API traffic that is entirely internal to your organization is normally called _?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`inbound traffic`","`north-south traffic `","`internal traffic `","`east-west traffic`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":46,"question":"What is the best approach for requesting JSON instead of XML from an API?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Add .json to the URL.`","`APIs do not use XML.`","`Use the Content-Type header.`","`Use the Accept header.`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":47,"question":"When a user attempts to access a record that is not their own, which HTTP response code is the most appropriate?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`403`","`404`","`401`","`405`"],"answer":[2]},{"id":48,"question":"Which is a benefit of using an API gateway?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`HTTP verbs`","`JSON payloads`","`HTTP response codes`","`rate limiting/throttling`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":49,"question":"API testing must be treated as **_**?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`red team testing`","`white box testing`","`blue box testing`","`black box testing`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":50,"question":"Which HTTP verb is used in a CORS preflight request?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`PUT`","`POST`","`GET`","`OPTIONS`"],"answer":[3]},{"id":51,"question":"Which response header will tell the client that the response is cached for 1 minute ?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`Expires: 1 minute`","`Cache-Control: max-age=60`","`Expires: 1 January 2020`","`Cache-Expires: max-age=60`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":52,"question":"What is the concept that allows an API client to explore an API via links embedded in payloads?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`hypermedia`","`link relations`","`parsing`","`browsing`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":53,"question":"Which HTTP response code describes a new resource as created successfully?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["`200`","`201`","`204`","`202`"],"answer":[1]},{"id":54,"question":"Which is an example of Code on Demand?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["AWS Lambda","downloading open-source software","Serverless","JavaScript on a webpage"],"answer":[3]},{"id":55,"question":"Which URL pattern should you follow for accessing a subresource attached to a specific resource?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["/companies/employees/{companyId}/{employeeId}","/company/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}","/companies/{companyId}/employees/{employeeId}","/companies/{companyId}/employee/{employeeId}"],"answer":[2]},{"id":56,"question":"Which REST constraint essentially prohibits the use of cookies?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["Stateless","Cacheable","Layered System","Uniform Interface"],"answer":[0]},{"id":57,"question":"Which HTTP verb is used to delete a resource?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["FLUSH","DELETE","CLEAR","DESTROY"],"answer":[1]},{"id":58,"question":"Which verb is _not_ considered idempotent?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["DELETE","GET","PUT","POST"],"answer":[3]},{"id":59,"question":"Which REST constraint specifies that each request should stand on its own and not have a specific required order?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["Uniform Interface","Cacheable","Stateless","Client-Server"],"answer":[2]},{"id":60,"question":"When you get a 429 code, what should you do next?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["Check you JSON structure.","Check the API uptime status.","Slow down your requests.","Check you API key."],"answer":[2]},{"id":61,"question":"When exploring record sets, what is the best approach for pagination?","code":"","reference":"","choices":["date-based filtering","next/previous cursors","page size and filters","database IDs"],"answer":[1]}]